Under Capricorn's mountain throne
With Aquarius dreams that chill to the bone
Mercury speaks with authority's fire
While Venus naps two left souls ever higher
Stormborn architect of impossible realms
Where shadows integrate and healing overwhelms
They call you dangerous for speaking what's true
But broken hearts find they're healing in you
Electric profit, lightning in your veins
Dancing with darkness, breaking all the chains
They shame what you carry, they fear what you see
But you're the bridge builder, setting spirits free
Your prophet crowned the lunar light
Psycho-pom walking mid-sweet, wrong and right
The outcasts find you the one to come home
You're never alone
Lilith and Scorpio power unveil
While Matangie's wisdom has never once failed
They hunt what you treasure, they mock what you need
But your sacred rebellion plants freedom seed
Reading the cosmos in cards and in dreams
Nothing is ever quite what it seems
Persecuted profit with love in your heart
Torn by their hatred, yet playing your
Electric profit, money in your veins, dancing with darkness, breaking all the chains, they shame what you carry, they fear what you see, but you're the bridge builder, setting spirits free.
Electric profit, crown the lunar light, cycle palm walking between wrong and right, the outcasts find you a-
They sing
Thank you. Oh, thank you so much, and I appreciate that rangers. How are you and I'm money for 20. How are you?
Um, I
Have my good shirt on I don't know the backwards
Oh, the north is staying my mouse. It's not a real mouse. Oh, baby. Oh, baby. Come on. Oh
There what's up guys?
kind of like try to rush a little bit to get here. I just like it's like it's weird like I just
like clicked on a video before like before I came in or I prefer to go to a bath right and
it was a Danny stranger video and I almost forgot I made that but it was like the I made him a song
just how to kind of I just did it really
Didn't like do a great video for it for him, but I mean that I put I played on the streaming art form and stuff
It's all true story
like I did well, it's kind of true because it's like
Ultimately, I mean, I think it would be kind of too weird to like buy somebody's underwear like that
but I
Don't know I think he might think he was pricing it kind of high too, but you know right now. I wish I had it
They took down the video like I don't know if he took down the video
It might be on his channel still where I went
Like I talked to him probably the day after
like all a lot of people from the chat came over to his chat and
He was like really happy
And he had a good time and he was and he was like and then I but I was like oh someone clips you
Someone clips you
Actually, so this is probably the night before when I was on a show, like someone clips you with the thing you're gay for pay
And he's like, I don't care
You think I'll be gay for pay? No, I don't know what they guess they took that video down
But maybe it's on his channel. I just have it. It's hard to kind of hard to watch
But I do like see him. Hi, Mermi. How are you?
I see him like
You know
He comes on my he's been coming on my feet a lot
But that's what was weird because he started disappearing on my feed, um,
before he passed away, like, a lot, and I, and I would, and I would,
went over there like quite, quite a few times because he would play video games and stuff.
And it's like, because I had been like, I didn't, like,
sometimes he didn't usually show up on my feed, so.
Um, but he started to show up on my feed a lot, and then they started to go in.
He was gay one time we were just like bullshit. He's like, oh, you're like you're like, why are you gay? Why are you gay?
Like this is teasing me and stuff. He's and then and I think I was so annoying like one of his mods
of his mods tied me out because I was I went too far or something, but but um
I think I did get to talk to him after that a couple times like when I'm turning in his truck driving and stuff and
He was really, really nice and he was always pretty nice to me.
The first time I went to his chat, he said, I was like, wow, I thought he was really cute.
And then I like, I think I used an emoji and he's like, well, he's like, who are you?
And there was not many people in this chat and he's like, who are you?
And I was like, I don't know, I just found you.
And I think I like use an emoji and he has this girl Mariah in there who he was like kind of dating sometimes
Do you hear me? Or is it the microphone?
But um
Yeah, and she's actually come over here too. I don't think she'd like me the very first time she met me
But she was pretty she was pretty cool
But he always had these girls in his chat like a few he's always like had like one girl or another like a
Like yeah, you know, there are always a few people in his chat
But then he get sometimes you'd be like
Why why is everyone just staring at me and then sometimes he'd be like
He'd be mad he'd get mad and stuff and I did refer to people a few weeks ago
Like probably not just it was probably more than a few weeks ago. I posted on my wall
Oh, you know I subscribed to him and I was trying to get people to and then like a few people were like, oh my god
I went over there. I
Love it was a troll. It wasn't a troll. It was like the guy that's gas station is like his local gas station
And it's like weird because I have another friend that was kind of like I told to watch him and
She saw like a she saw a clip of like she saw him one night at the gas station and he got in like a fight there and like
Kind of like this is yelling at people and stuff, but yeah somebody
Like saw him and then they thoroughly I think they thought he brandished a gun or something
I'm I don't know 100% the story for sure, but it is on his stream
Like he like left his camera on the gas station was nearby and so you hear the gunshots
You're like three gunshots and stuff like that and I actually saw that I saw that he was on like on that Sunday
I saw it like he was on I saw that like that stream and I didn't go over there because it
The stream was like, oh, everyone don't subscribe.
I don't like anybody.
And so, but as they always in a bad mood and stuff.
So I didn't go over there.
That was like last stream.
And I guess his mom came and turned it off or something.
But I knew him for like, before I started the show,
if you know Piranha,
Piranha, like I introduced her to him.
And
Like like one night like I think I gave him like $35 so he modded me
But so he would dance and stuff. I don't want him to dance this underwear
I don't know if you heard the song about me play it again later soon, but um
And so he actually did and like it was so funny, but then it's like I went kind of went too far like and like
But I was just like I had but he didn't care. He didn't care, but um
But it's really sad because piranha like really fucking fucked up
You know
She actually put in a good word for me with him and stuff cuz he I think like I
Was banned from his chat they got one point and then like I like told her to go over there
And she said oh I'm banning him and so you unbanned me and then every time I went there after that
He was really nice and he really liked her and so it was and so but
Dan piranha fell out after the show and then like probably several months later
Like I tried to get her over to the show again, and I was talking to her on like I like I think discord or something like that or something and
We talked for like one day and then the next day and then she was like always like she was like very very terse of me and like sometimes and then she was like
Finally one day she's like oh, she's like well either you just go you go get a normal job
Or I'm never gonna talk to you again, or I'm not gonna talk to you
You have to get a normal job or something and I was just so insulted that I just I just blocked her and so I hadn't talked to her since then and then
You know shortly like before Danny passed away
He asked about her and he's like hey, where's where's pie? Why did pie come see me anymore?
I'm like, I don't know. She's not very nice to me anymore. He's like, oh, I liked her and you know
He thought she was cool and stuff
And so then like last night or the night before something I got a message like on my what's app?
I think and it was her and she's like she's like, oh you're on here. Oh wow cool. Hi. It's pie Rana or whatever
And I was like, oh is it then I was like, oh, I'm sorry to tell you
Danny passed away and then like my phone died and like a couple of hours later. I saw she said oh
Yeah, I know
And then I said, I said, you know, he asked about you,
like when he always, you know, you know how I was,
he was like, he says, you're a ladies man.
And then I looked at the phone and she had said,
you, well, that was a great conversation.
Bye, or something like that.
It was just like so,
like, I was like, oh, I blocked her again.
It's like, I don't know why, but just weird for her to say, you, like, well, of course
he was like, he was like, you know, he loved, you know, he always had like a couple of girls
like he was interested in, like that would come in this chat, but I think most of like
his stuff, like, you know, he had like, people like, I think people were minding him some
stuff near the end, because he was like, at one point he was like, a couple of weeks
You're like a red robe like this is long and it is like kind of like it looks like he like
He's like
like I think like the candles or something in his in his trailer and
His cat we give this cat. It's really cute cat. Hey fucking look. How are you get a cat and
Which I hardly even saw
but
Yeah, and then
Then I kind of like I told the chat like one night to go to his chat
And I think he went from like three or four people to like 40 people and I went over there
a couple of times during that and he was just talking to people and all energized.
And then the next day it was kind of like back to normal but he still had a couple more
people than usual and I saw it like he didn't have people I know go in there and stuff like
and so that and then like that week, like just a few days later.
It's like that happened on some and I didn't know and then like someone told me on discord
And I was like I just didn't believe it because I I've been told like a lot of times that people
died like one time someone told me Joker and our lives himself
In vent in a try and shut and then
someone told yeah, the bodies told me that you know that a
Popola had died and stuff and then
They both turned out to be alive, but then you know and then but unfortunately Michael did pass away and Michael did like he's another person that like I
Hung out with him and like piranha and stuff before like I guess he has like a thing with piranha
And like you know, she was kind of mean to him afterwards and she's like oh my god Michael's ready me this time
She kind of liked him, but then she thought he was kind of weird. He told me he also told me his mom
Died one time and then it's like I found out she was alive. So just Mike Michael did you know?
I was like just think I was like who would say their mom that could I just be
like just to say that and it's not true I think why would you do that like not
even like it's like a caribbean life you better say why I just like I just felt
like those are bad luck or something to say something like that and why I don't
know why he did then of course hey Chanel how are you then of course he was
like you know
Got really more involved in this community and stuff and like then he was dating Tracy
Actually, I found him in this transgender's room, and I've shown this transgender to God. It looks like
Harvey Fierstein in a way it's a it's no it's no flirty diamond
I'll hate to say that like flirty diamond is like Pamela Anderson or something appeared at this trend and this trans
This trans I was in this trans chat, and he kept having Tracy like hide me and stuff because I went to this Femios's
chat when he saw me there one night and he's like, he's like, oh, you're talking to Femios?
Femios?
I think they're, I guess, they're mortal enemies because Femios was more feminine and
with like, kind of teasing that he looked like Harvey Fierstein or, kind of, I don't
know.
He was just, I wish I had a picture, the name is Sabrina T.W. of the trans, but Michael,
Michael and Tracy were Mazen there and Michael was the donator and stuff to her.
He goes, hi, my prettys. Hi. And just like, just like, has big like chin and like, just like really like, uh,
I showed him to Gaudi and Gaudi was like, oh my god, what, who, what is that?
I'll just say no flirty diamonds. Flirty diamonds like,
Flirty diamonds actually pretty, pretty good.
Flirty diamond has like a feminine face in a certain way, like a more feminine face.
Like that a lot of trans would like die to have, you know, it's like,
Especially because she's not technically like, you know post-op or whatever
Even though
She is lactating apparently
And that will because that when then when I didn't jokers chat like he bought the only thing
I think maybe Pita gave him the money to buy like her
Only fans to find out like what was in there and it was just like one picture of
Squirting some kind of liquid out of the breast
Um
I don't know I don't know I
Don't understand everything about it, but it's kind of interesting. So oh my gosh, so I don't know
I'm a good night. I did like a and the
Let's see. Oh, there's five people in here. So like nobody's really here. Okay. That's good
Well, I guess like either people probably stick of me either because I've been posting a lot of like
music videos and then like, you know
I would think there'd be more people because I think there'd be more people because of
kind of like the publicity, but it's all bad publicity of course for me.
But it's just so interesting how like the rules just seem to apply to me, but they don't
apply to anybody else that's applying these rules on me, like why are they making these
rules?
Isn't that kind of like almost like controlling the narrative, right?
Like I think there's a desperate to control the narrative like
But in doing the control in the narrative they are really
And they'll say that I'm slandering them or whatever I'm saying terrible thing
But I'm saying is like nothing compared to what they're saying about me
I'm a child, or I'm, you know,
Lilith is a mirror of babies and children.
And I'm like, Mike, the cult is about like, you know,
doing that, like, I don't know,
it's just the sickest shit.
And then it's like, and then of course,
chat GPT is just a simp, simp, syncopant,
syncopant, syncopant.
And it's like, if you phrase things in chapter GPT
a certain way, of course it's gonna answer a certain way.
It's gonna, if you say,
Oh, okay, so there's a, hey, Kim, can you say to chat GPT?
There's this, like, 44-year-old white...
I'm part Jewish guy that is a cult leader and he is worshiping the child devouring
demon Lilith
and and and and there's no contact on him and he's
You know, I mean it's like just like the way the way it's phrased it makes it
Catch me. He's like, oh my gosh
Well, this guy sounds like all these mental problems and he's like a cult leader and stuff like I mean it's just like
It's not it's kind of taking things like a little bit out of context, you know
not even a little bit like way way out of context, but and that's it is very insulting to
Like this anti-semitism that's been expressed. I've never seen anybody like
Talk like that unless they're like, you know
They've usually have Nazi uniforms on after talking like that, especially throwing good times of night into an oven really you're gonna say that
Good times and I aren't even Jewish by the way, but we're offended we're offended for them. I
mean that is just ridiculous and
Saying dirty Jews, you know, I don't know. It's just like I
Didn't I can't believe that side is coming out of you, but that is
Just personally
That's ugly, that's ugly side
And it's like, yeah, you're lucky that the inside doesn't always reflect the outside
and you don't look like the inside.
You know, I might be ugly or whatever, like you said, and I might smell and I might just
like, you know, be the worst person in the world.
I mean, it's just like, just the stuff that it said, oh my God, it's just like, oh, hours
and hours and then it's, oh, and you know, and then Christine's up doing that too.
Christine's terrible.
And I was told like oh, yeah, she's not really she didn't really forgive you or she was she was kind of like
It's taking the opportunity to come and come in and kind of like gather intel or something like that or just kind of like
Mindfuck you a little bit. Like, you know
Like I like people were telling me like she was saying they were seeing her say stuff
You know behind like another chest and stuff that I would always kind of like just kind of see a little bit of it
But she came on to good times this morning I was in good times and
We had a good chat with good times and stuff. I am jealous of good times here. Oh, yeah
So this person guys if you ever see this person my mods Chanel you're gonna see this look you see his name
Just always just being that person like and whoever that it's just Tony
It's Tony and stuff. It's just always been the person. I have a terrible hair
I mean my my hairline that terrible is it really I
Mean it's not wearing a wig or anything. I think like you know
Yeah, I do have like these little like things my dad had these and so I like them
But yeah, he says really really bad things plus
Plus he sent over today
Or I think it was him it might have been someone else because she did say I would get a knock on my door
And I did get some knocks on my door some pizzas
Unpaid pizzas and actually the the water some water company was about to shut off my water
He was told like oh your father called and oh and by the way they said it was from Christine
Like and so or for Chris. Yeah, the pizzas were for Christine
I don't know who but they said it was my father that called my father passed away, of course
But um, you know, I had explained to the water company. He said I was just about to turn off your water
I'm lucky I'm lucky I knocked on your door and stuff. He's like, are you serious? He's like what?
He's like, what's going on? Like
People people are like they will do that for you know
Pretty shocking but
You know it's happened before with the gas company
But the good thing was that the police did actually come after that because it's like this serious things
How would they to be messing with people's utilities and had and these companies doing emergency calls and wasting all their time and and all that
And so the police were called to my house because of it to question me about it
And I told them all I knew and they gave me some great advice and I don't know somehow
After that it pretty much slowed down, but
You know, no, I don't know. It's like it doesn't I mean it wasn't like anybody
Everybody I would tell about it didn't just laugh at me and say oh, that's so funny like it's like oh, it's a but it's funny
It wasn't really funny to me, but
Anyway, I was able to
Care of it, but anyway, so Christine would say well Christine I was in on Stephen King's chat who I met the other day and I went in
And she said, oh no, she modded me right away.
And of course she wanted to like hide me immediately.
And then she just started bitching and bitching
and I was in there.
But when she was on Good Times this morning,
she, I was like, oh, I was excited to see her
when I went to talk to her.
She's like, oh, you know, you're just like awful
and blah, blah, blah.
And I was like, well, I was like, I was joking.
And she's like, oh, I don't care about it.
You don't joke.
You don't joke about that.
And then I said, well, what about you joking about it?
about me jumping off a bridge or your son jumping up
and then, or yeah, me jumping, I should jump off a bridge.
She's like, well, I'm serious about that.
I said, so you can be serious about me jumping off a bridge.
But if I joke about, you know, something that's obviously
a joke and a satire and, you know, whatever,
it's not, it's like, it's just a double standard.
And then she's like, and then she was,
then I eventually left because I was just sick of her.
And she said, oh, you know, you don't need to,
he deletes his streams.
And then good times is like, well, I know somebody else
that deletes their streams.
I don't know, I'll say their name starts with B
or something like that.
And she's like, oh, well, she deletes all her streams.
But this person, he deletes only the ones
where he's talking shit about us.
It's like, miserable.
And then, oh, and then it's like,
now the big thing is that they're so mad.
It's like, hold her granny or grandma or something.
Like, apparently.
She's close like she's close to my age, and I'm old. I'm really old now or something
Well, I'm not in my like 70s or whatever like she is. I mean, but I mean, I guess I'm like, yeah
I'm around Alice's age, but I
Don't know but it just seems like it's like like why is it's so like why I mean it's just so
Bitch we all like against me. I can't how are you sweetheart?
Um, yeah, it was really, I wish I could, I wish a good time to like let me play that
or something like that.
I would love people to see how it was treated and stuff like that.
Um, there's a lot of times I would like to see how it was treated, but it's like, you
know, it's usually not on my show.
They don't come over here unless they're like trying to cause trouble.
Like they did like the other week.
Now Katie now that woman Katie not Kate Kate, but you know like Katie and you know Katie and Jamie and stuff
Like I said I made a joke because when I woke up the other night and it's like and Jamie had said
Well, hope it was worth it in two years
And you just like you know let me pick them over me because I had like modded somebody that and said reach hard or something like that
And so I got kind of hurt and, you know,
because I kept getting like a fucking, like just like,
people just like, because I was blocked
when I tried to reply and stuff.
So I had said on the show,
oh, there was like Thelma and Louise, they went and, you know,
off towards the Grand Canyon, I don't know,
or like they went to like, you know,
buy a house in Vermont or something dumb joke.
And now Katie has written me saying she's going to be suing me
for saying that she's a lesbian.
And, you know, on top of the, you know, the other lawsuit, I mean, it's like, I don't know, I mean, I don't really have much to, you know, to sue for, but I don't know.
But I have figured out a lot of stuff, and it's kind of like just disheartening. I figured out, like, I was targeted, you know, and I don't know how many people are involved in this.
You know the front person for it or for was for that time, right?
And I'm not trying to be paranoid and have these conspiracy theories like her
It's honestly, I do know because it's like up the way
They're using it like they're taking every like little bit of information like I shared or every little like in security
We just every single thing and they're just like trying to push push it and so that takes me to another thing
It's like this like, you know
Deciding to call me a fraudulent psychic. Okay
Like not even like just just forget about you know
Me me like doing readings and doing it for a living and stuff and me doing it since I was eight
Let's just forget all that let's just say
You're not God you're not God you don't get to say
What's you know, okay Connors but like how like I really I really am kind of just confused about it
But as for like my abilities those are gifts and they're not for you to like judge
You're not God and no matter how much you think you are, right?
That I'm not I mean, you know, you know I'm talking about I mean and that that person is just like, you know, because I'm apparently just like, you know
The cult is like so maybe that's why there's no one here is like because I think it's like some kind of child devouring cult now
Like it's like there's two episodes today and like two more minutes made about that about about, you know
Lilith who's like I was just saying
Like I know Lilith, I mean it's like it's so funny like Lilith's actually, have you heard of Lilith Fair?
Have you heard of like, you know, different things? Lilith actually, you know, may have been in like some
pseudographia texts
demonized a little bit like but that's
you know a demonized woman and it's like
because it was easy to demonize a woman so they can blame her for everything, right?
Just like Eve is kind of demonized too, but
Or even at least blamed, you know lives really demonized because Lilith is the one devouring the over killing killing
So anyway that they keep trying to save over and over killing killing killing, you know
It just makes it sound it just sounds so horrible and stuff, which is not even the thing
It's like I've always seen it for her as a symbol of
Rebellion and empowerment and of like, you know not having to
having the ability to walk away or like not having to like be in the status quo
of like just a normal life and I'm not saying like you know there's you know
there's ease but I mean it's kind of I really I really am getting sick of
being lectured by like you know by a former porn star about the Bible and
Christianity and stuff and it's just like so stupid but here's the thing
You know, it wouldn't be weird like you can't you cuz you can imagine like right now you would like the way it sounds like
You know, she would never like she doesn't you know
The caro would be against the Bible and stuff and she's been religious for all this time
Right like because she was doing the same shit to other people like la la like let's say this lady Lauren
La la you go back like a year ago. She's like friends with Zaya in the chat or in the comments
like picking on her and stuff. I mean it's just like the cycle of like these rotating characters right?
Did you know about that? You can go back and see that. Um oh my gosh um yeah you're a dolphin
fucker. Hold on one second. Actually a dolphin wouldn't even want to fuck you because you're too
I got I got I'm too fast. I'm too fast. I guess guys the mods if you see if you ever see people like that
Especially like that is like, you know, trying to like docks, you know me and stuff like that you can
Just be as fast as you can just get them out here. I don't want to see my baby. Oh, you're kissing, you know, you know
It's okay. I love you
Not saying it's like I'm not mad. I'm just like I'm gonna stick to that guy, you know
Oh, then this, then this, and then this, like also this narrative of me being a stalker of all these women and being obsessed with all these women, you know, and it turns out, you know what these women did?
They're all bullies.
Hey, 2020, these women are bullies that they're talking about, except for Lisa Jordana, who she mentioned, like she said, Lisa said, leave her the fuck alone, like, and stop talking about her.
At least I never said that like at least I never had a problem. I've been still in Lisa's discord and I'm a personal friend with her
like I'm able to like, you know
right here on discord personally
It's these other like
There are three miserable hags that I don't know why I spent so much time trying to preserve a friendship
But now it's like, you know, oh, there's talking about it
I mean it's like and now it's turned into like oh, there's all these women behind the scenes it seems like right
It's just a lie
It's a lie.
I'd like them to come forward.
Come forward, please.
And you don't have to come on my show.
Go on hers.
Tell the whole story.
Tell whatever you think.
Yeah, let's just see.
There's not there.
Oh, I know.
I love you.
I have a respect for women.
And it's like, but yeah, there's just so much to it.
It's just like, so.
Disheartening, but it's like I really do feel like I was just I was just like, you know, I was just
picked to fucking
Humiliate or something like that or some kind of like something there's something weird with all of it, you know, hi
Especially because it's like you know now she's you think she okay
So she oh she sounds like she's really against like witchcraft and stuff this lady because she's all into the Bible and stuff
And so against the Lilith who's often known as the queen of witchcraft, right?
But look at they'd like look at two days ago
She was doing a stream about how she's a she's like a witch from her African tribe who knows how to control the weather and
You know Christine's a witch and you know, they're all
So so excited so proud of that, but it's like
Anything to do with the me saying it. It's like some kind of disgusting, you know
murdering, you know
Baby goats or whatever which I would never just it's just like so sick. It's really sick
Bible spiritual cope. Yeah, I mean I really I mean I think yeah a lot of it is a lot of it
I mean some of it there's some there's some good story
It's like the vibe was a lot of books a lot of texts like put together and a lot of old some of them are legends and some of them
Like are we know there's interesting stuff in there. I like that. I like some songs and stuff, but
basically
organized religion is like, you know, I think kind of a controlled mechanism, but
you know it's really funny it's these people with crosses on their neck that like say they're Christians
and it's like they're probably would have been spitting on Christ on the cross
Like really the way they talk especially the way they talk about Jews, you know
Jesus was like born a Jew so and all of most of these people in the Bible were Jews
Like I don't know what you'd be saying dirty Jews and in this boy wearing a cross around your neck and at the same time like
You know saying you're gonna throw me in the oven
Picturing me crucified
picturing me, you know burning a dumpster picturing me, you know kissing your ex-boyfriend who never really loved you
You know, it's like I mean
I don't want to be like so petty, but it's like, I mean, really.
And then all these pictures, I even look at the littlest pictures
that she was doing, but she was doing these terrible, littlest pictures.
My hands brown because it like, once again,
because I think you breathe near it.
Hold on. There you go. I got it before.
I am brown guys
I haven't just taken a bath. I don't know. Yeah, I guess this is I'm just, you know
So dirty, right?
Yeah, oh, yeah, I smell too according to her, right? It's raining coats harder to cipher. Oh, it's hard easy to go
Yeah, so what I did with the bible is like, um, I read I read
Basically these cabala bibles
like a few years ago and
What you do it's like there there's like there's like the texts of the Bible and then there's like like these
Combalistic explanations. There's also Aramaic, which is the original languages that it was written in. It's also written in Greek, too
Like some of them, some of the new testimonies were written in Greek. The Old Testament is in Aramaic, which is like the stylized Hebrew
It's a really pretty really pretty style of Hebrew
But our Hebrew came off of it, right?
And it's like you just scan it. Yeah, it's written in code. Yeah, that's part of the code
Well, there's also the Midrash, which is like see the first five books in the Bible are called the Torah
And then there's like the Midrash, which is like the oral tradition, which was like not really written down until much later and it has more
Controversial things in it than the King James. Yeah, well, I think King James was just Shakespeare, right?
Or it was like the council of Nicaea, which was just the same thing as Shakespeare basically
At the end of the day, yeah
And he looked looks out of it. Yeah, he also changed a lot of things like he changed a lot of a lot of the original
Symbolism into different things like there's unicorns in it and shit
And I mean Eve our races blood types not people. Yeah, there's also like, you know, so our San Miguel and Lilith are also
our like
Kind of like the reproductive fluids or something like that more than
you know, angel and demon, but I mean that this is gonna be kind of, kind of
Esoteric for most people and so I let people discover some of this on their own
But it's just like you know, but I think the whole thing is it's like
There's this like desperation to control some kind of narrative and it's like okay
No
You're not gonna you're not gonna like
Take this narrative that I am like this like
I mean, it's like, it's the destruction of my character.
Like, really, it's like, it's like a homicide of my character, right?
So like you know, and she would you know, I like I said chat GPT is very syncopatic
So she had a couple streams today where she's going through about chat GPT and all the things chat GPT
You know it's chat GPT apparently just hates me and stuff right here, right?
But it's like it's just the way she's phrasing stuff makes it sound really bad like she said
Oh, well this person has no contact and I and not and I'm never gonna panel with them and and then
She's she like has literally come on the panel after she said that on my panel
and so
How is that like is that me going over she do you I don't mean I just don't know
False accusation like spiritual trafficker is literally a sin. I know and
You know and it's not just me. It's like
There's a lot of people like I don't know it's like and I feel like like a lot of people have been just bullied into
Silence or embarrassed or just like or it's like just so insane. It's like oh my god
I'll just leave this alone
And nobody like will stand up for a really because you know, she's very well-spoken. She's very you know
She's a very beautiful, you know, you know, I'm beautiful woman, but you know
Trying to think like I mean
So so was you know, probably Elizabeth Bathory was
Beautiful and we know what she did right? I mean, it's like just because you're a queen. I mean, you know, it's like
Doesn't mean you're a good person. I mean, that's a quick industry and then because I'm
I'm apparently so ugly and dirty that I'm just filthy spiritually, right?
And it's like and then it's just like I'm covered in cat hair. Well, yeah, I do have like five cats
I don't brush my teeth. I don't know. Do you really get that close repeat like you know, and it's like and this is a person that
I've heard accused of like getting fired from the porn industry for her, her, her, you know, body odor and stuff.
I mean, and it's like, I never really ever repeat that. I was like, the whole thing is, I felt like she understood.
Like, that's the whole thing. It's like, it's like gaining this trust and stuff by like, by trying to say, oh, well, they said this about me.
And I was like, wow, they said the same things about me. So I relate to that. And it's like, I got so close.
And then it's just like, the rug was pulled under from me.
And then it's like, and that's why I sometimes flounder a little bit like and try to like repair a friendship because it's like I, I like sometimes develop a lot of love and attachment and like affection for them for them, but I was never, I never bothered her.
You know, it's like, I would support her as much as I could. I would, you know, she would call in the middle of the night and sometimes she'd fall asleep on the phone or I'd fall asleep or something like that.
It's all fake. It really was just it was just really fake because it's like how can you change so much? How can you go from?
Getting 10 readings from me
How can you go from getting 10 readings from me?
At least and buying reading for other people and so but then it's like the year before
You were like in this this crazy kind of Christian thing, too
Where it's like if I would have met you then you wouldn't have liked tarot, but how did I it's just a very confusing, right?
It's a kind of like a mind fuck, you know, which I think it's probably designed to be and so
Yeah, I just feel like it's
Like how far is this supposed to go? I mean, it's like I'll fight I'll fight for myself
I'm not gonna let myself just be silenced and then have you running around
Continuing to say this shit like you do by everybody else all the time all the time all the time and then it's like
And I don't even see I don't even see these other people anymore. Really. It's like, you know
And it doesn't get I don't know. It just it's like it seems like it's dangerous, you know, it's like but you know
I'm not afraid though, it's like, I, uh, I dealt with like a terrible point, even like
when I was in like third, fourth, fifth grade or something, I was bullied by these girls
in my school and they would call and like, they would call my house and at like, like
they'd call and like they'd, they'd, they'd, they'd, they'd like me and stuff like that
and I was like kind of like a, kind of dorky, dorky like, you know, kid or whatever.
Then they would like
You know get really nasty and like, you know, there's I think they were just like a slumber party or something like calling him fucking
He wants me to start joining his panels. Well, I don't
All I say is like when I it's just like I kind of like
Don't want to join panels. It's like I'm just coming to fool over wherever I go
No
I think I'm just safer and like better off here or else I'll just be accused of
But stalking him next so I mean it's like please I can't even go to another show without being I don't want to be the queen of the
hoovers I don't
I want to be the king of my own life not the queen of some like you know ghetto please
Or whatever whatever the Hoover gang or is it Hoover gang they have the I mean it what is it like everything is a cleaning appliance
There's like the broom gang the Hoover gang
It's like I'm not interested in just you know, I don't like to clean
Why I don't I don't I don't even own a broom or vacuum. I'm just kidding. I do I do own them
But I'm not in those gangs or affiliated at all nor do I want to be
Yeah, it's Q Qs here
How is everyone doing like I did like but yeah, I was like I was gonna like drink my drink after cuz I made this like a little
Little memorial for Danny. It's like it's not it's just like so a few like a couple months ago. I I
Made this dumb song for him and stuff. Oh the window. Yeah, the Windex and the bleach gang
Oh my god, Windex everything Windex everything up informed. I don't own a Bremen vacuum
I actually do I have a vacuum right here. Look so few proof wrong
You see a few in here actually.
I'm gonna do a room too.
So, but I'm not in the Hoover gang, I promise, okay?
So, but I do wanna play this,
this is like a little memorial for Dan.
So a couple months ago, I think I did make this song for him
and I went on a show and I played it for him
and it's like, it's just based on a true story,
but he got a kick out of it.
And then I saw this video that would go perfect with it,
where he like, that,
You know, I didn't put the part in the video where he's actually drinking the drinks
And so I'm gonna like and I want you to guys to hear his voice and stuff
So I'll drink I'll chug I'll chug the drink when you drink so we can play it
Okay, so this is um, this is just like one of his like from one of his streams
And this is a stupid song that I wrote but it was kind of it's kind of funny, but um, this is like, you know
He passed away on
couple Sundays ago, I think that, you know, he was shot in the chest three times.
Really tragic. He was in his 30s, left behind two,
I think two daughters and stuff, and he had a cat, too. He just got a cat and stuff, and I
think it's, I think it's kind of a cute video, so
Bear with me.
Danny stranger walking in like a county fair star
Looking so cute got that kid rock guitar bar
I'm actin' normal, yeah, sure, okay
But my brain's yellin' open, I made your way
He did one little dance, and my soul said,
Fine, now I'm losin' my dignity one beat at a time
I don't hit him up much, I keep it tight
Cause he's got that charm that can wreck my night
One smile, one hate, and I'm already sure
He'll talk me into somethin' expensive, look
Danny stranger, you're trouble, you're cute
I wanna buy your underwear and your socks in a pack
You danced for me once, now I'm down bad facts
But I'm keeping it casual while I'm losing my tracks
And no, he ain't gay, so don't make it weird
I'm just out here spiraling crystal clear
I don't talk to him much, cause I know what he'll do
He'll talk me into buying him a whole dang truck
And I don't even ever bike dude
Got that I might be a problem grand Like he's selling sunshine with a citizen
He laughs, I fold my wallet, get scared I'm tryna play cool but I'm deeply unprepared
I'm not sayin' I'm obsessed Just molly deranged like who needs self-respect
When the vibes is strange I keep my distance, I do my best
But he pops in my head like a bad text He says we should hang, I'm like maybe soon
Man says, babe, in my brain, go spend money.
I'm not his bank, I'm not his plan.
I'm just a humble fan with a morally questionable stance.
If he blinks twice, I'm making poor choices.
Hearing cash registers like background voices.
But I'm keeping it casual while I'm losing my track
So no, he ain't gay, so don't make it weird
I'm just out here spiraling crystal clear
I don't talk to him that much, cause I know what he'll do
He'll talk me into buying him a whole dang truck
And I don't even have a bike, dude
Danny Stranger
Please stop being adorable
My finances can't take it.
Well, I'll finish the rest of it now.
Here we go.
He was shot cutting beers.
The two beer challenge, do you not know what it is?
Well, we need to why?
I'm just gonna shotgun two beers back to back
from a water bottle, because why not?
We are quarantined, you know, and I don't see why I can't.
I got beers, I got water bottles and I have the time
to do so, so we are going to go ahead and do just that.
Now we're gonna see how fast I can get done with two of these
Obviously, I got a pause for the first one and come back the second one
But we're going to see what we can do to finish them both
I will leave them both on screen so you know, it's actually alcohol and not some sort of apple juice
mixture
What an order. All right, whatever
So we're gonna go ahead and do that and
Where I was doing this do me a favor
Reach out to all your loved ones. Let them know you love them. I won't but we should do that
I'm not a dick. I just don't look I don't spend a lot of my time on my phone. I don't
It's just I it's it's in my pocket or next to the couch. I don't spend a lot of time on my phone
All my notifications are off. So
They reach out to me cool
Not fuck whatever
That's cool too
Okay
Hi kitty
That one right here on screen, so I'm gonna I'm gonna slam this one and immediately grab that one and slam that one as well
I gotta put my cat down on the ground cuz
The pretty nosey
Do not try this at home. I am a trained beer drinking out of a water bottle professional. No, you don't need to get up there
All right, don't need to get up there. Quit it. Quit trying to get up there. Quit. Wait a minute. All right
Stretch my arms gotta stretch you gotta get they get in the mood for it
I've never shotgun back to back
I'm probably gonna puke
I'll let's say two beers in one second, but I physically can't shotgun two beers in one second
So we're gonna shotgun one and then shotgun another one
Cheers
Don't judge me for drinking Coors like damn it. I love the taste of it, right? I
Got to get that bottle ready to actually know that I thought about it
Always lose just a little bit, but now it's I would scrunch down so I can actually grip it. All right, here we go
Anyways
That's the two beer challenge y'all can
Suck in them faster than me
Hats off to you if you can't try harder
Cue
He drank him fast. I didn't know he was gonna like pop drink like that to his pop up like that to his mouth
Everybody I was over there watching. So hi everybody
I'll put the link in
Right I think I think to see him
Quite a bit like
Yeah, you might, I mean, it's like, you know, he had, he had, he was kind of wild and stuff.
But he was always nice to me.
And I never got to buy and I did like, you know, I did ask about underwear and stuff
It was too expensive. You know, it's really funny. Like I was like, well, I was like, well, how much is your wife beater?
He's like, it's not a wife beater. It's not a wife beater. It's called a white beater. And I said, no, they're called wife
wife beaters not white beaters
He honestly still like anything and it's like I wouldn't think he
He would have like worn it enough to like
Didn't know it. They're called wife beater. He's like, they're called wife beater. He's like, that's funny
white beaters, it's hilarious. But his channel is still up and stuff, and I don't think I've
ever heard that, and I don't think he would have known. Kind of funny. So I'm going to
He talked to me before like, you know, he called me like about 10 or like it may be a nine
And he's like then he's like go live
And so I was like I was gonna play the video or even premiere the video and then I said oh
Then I'll be just like out of the bath and I'll come and I guess I thought I wasn't quick enough
So that's a real show player. Oh my god
Do I wear white Peters? I mean
I think I have like a couple and you know, you wear black beaters. I'm just like too skinny
Like I mean, it's like it's just not like doesn't look like good on me, you know, but oh Lenore. Hi, baby. I wish you know
Wish I look good in them. I mean, but I think you look good. That's why I like that video
But you know you also be like
Sometimes you'd have a shirt off a lot too and I like that
But and then he like I said he danced for me once for like $35 and he modded me
He like unmodded me like the next day and then and I he like started like charging me like $5 every time
I hit on him and then it was like up to $400 and I like Ted is like
The knock it was chat until he like had forgotten about that
It was just a cute story, you know?
That was like, um...
Oh yeah, he wanted me to buy him a truck. That's what the song was about, you know?
He was like, I was gonna...
Eventually, he would have like, you know, I would have had enough to buy him a Ford range,
but I just couldn't afford it.
You know, he never charged me for anything but that.
But he didn't involve me the next day.
And, uh...
I mean, that was like, you know, over a year ago.
And, uh, that was when I, like, piranha and stuff...
Piranha was really bad.
And I told her because he had asked about her and stuff recently because I introduced them
and I guess she didn't care or something or she didn't like it because I said, I said,
oh, he said, yeah, he was, you know, I said, you know, he asked about you because, you
know, he was quite the ladies man or whatever, or you love the ladies or whatever.
So I just blocked her for the second time.
So, but I don't know, yeah.
So there's 12 people here.
So I guess like everything is like, you know,
working out for the other person's favor.
So she'll probably get her wish.
But my wish for her is that she someday something grows a heart, you know
It's like very
Cold how she did how she went about things
Very calculated, and I don't know if there's other people involved in it, but I'm almost feeling that
I'm gonna find the some videos too
of her appearances. Well, actually, you know, it shows this one video, but I need to find
out, you know, I do have these appearances I have mostly private right now, but she was
around quite a bit. If you remember, but people never remember like that. They always like
to just remember like the bad stuff, right? I'll find something cool. I'll be right back.
Okay, let's see.
And was it, it was like,
I remember I got my channel taken down in like,
October 21st or something, three weeks.
No, no, it got back on the beginning.
Oh, no, no, it was Halloween,
or it was about Halloween,
like the 30th where it got taken down, so.
But for that
Let's see we're just a January so far December
But I remember she was the first person I told like the channel was down
she was probably the first person I told it was back up and stuff too and
Maybe there's some videos. Okay, so we're now in October. Okay, so
Three weeks, okay
Hi, Ruby. Oh my gosh, but some of my
Some of my
Lives
Octo how long were they? Okay, they were short. Okay, maybe that's why I don't know. Oh shit. I'm not even in my lives
Oh, fuck. Okay. Fuck
December and it's like someone I was just looking at someone from my videos have zero
Zero likes or dislikes
See
Okay
Goes tober fast you remember it goes tober fast guys that was quite a crazy month right goes tober
if I can, if there's, I use her name anywhere,
it's like, I can see her picture somewhere, I don't know.
I don't, it's like, I do have thousands and thousands
of episodes, October 5th, so okay, so this is before, okay.
So, I haven't seen a lot of these in a while.
Maybe I should prepare once in a while, you know.
I have something prepared, but.
Or in September I remember mr. Goodpipes would come over and he was a her streamer of the month and
it's like and
Everyone would tell me oh, he's just he's her spy
And I was like what and I would just hear about I didn't know who she was and I'd see I then I saw her on the panel
That's oh, she looks
She's interesting
Okay, so I guess yeah the troll pedia in that time
Okay, I think I might have run that time
It'll just fuck you say it's up to go to my shorts or something as I see her in a thumbnail
See what that's one of the most hated man on YouTube
Actually, I can go to my now I can go to cold codex and I can figure out exactly when
Go like oh my gosh, what's happening here?
My god, it's seeing that is I think it is was back then back then there's a lecture
And I guess I'll just go to my shorts salute my shorts right here we go
Let's see if I can find some shorts.
A lot of stuff I had to private though,
it's like, and that's like Christina's like,
oh, he's privates everything.
Well, oh, and then I think I do see, I said,
I see the episode with the raid and I was so lucky
because the episode before that got struck.
And so it's down, and that was only a minute long.
Wow, I got struck for a minute long clip, but it sucks.
About talking about AIR or something, okay.
See, this is still February, so yeah, I have so many shorts.
I'm sorry guys, I'm just like, hi Rudy, hi.
There's a little week meow.
There'll be a little meow, here.
There's like, okay, there's Christmas time. Yeah, so it happened or I remember exactly what happened. It happened December 19th
That was like the end of it, but
It was like supposed to be
Spun Christmas extravaganza
There were some good times and not good times for life, but it's good times
See if I have any clips of that though
Hi, everybody. Yes, you ready?
Hi
Oh, there's autos for assistant others, but I'm now remembering this. Wow, guys, there's so many
so funny how time is it there's so much
moments
Uh-oh, hold on a second
Can't hear me
Hello everybody
I just came to say what's up the site.
I hope he's having a good night tonight.
I just wanted to understand what his memes were about.
I can't pull it up on screen, but I saw a meme of his on his community tab.
It actually made me laugh.
I'll read it out for you.
It says, imagine.
Wait, okay. This is what it says
Imagine doing a Bible study with someone who calls you a friend first and a human trafficker next. I just want to understand
What these memes mean?
Imagine Queen Jezebel and the prophet Elijah re-incarnating in the present day to settle the score on an open panel. I
Just want to know what this is about. This is it's just kind of intriguing
Other than that
I'll just say what's up
Your mic is muted
You're a snub twice for a streamer of the month
You want to hop on and give me a few minutes to view and all that shit like in a view? Oh, yeah
Okay, I'm sorry. I was like I was just looking for shorts, but I'm sorry. I got kind of like
distracted and I was like, you know, hey, how are you a joker? How are you? I saw you with what's this here?
You left me for clumsy now
No, no, I saw that you posted a meme and I just wanted to ask you about it
So it says imagine Queen Jezebel and Prophet Elijah
Yeah, is that who were you who are like who are you battling?
It was this mysterious goddess. You don't know who that is
Well, you've been you've really been right
Not by the AI depiction of them. I can't tell
This is is this anybody tell by the AI depiction. Oh, well, I don't know
I think it's kind of obvious if you know the person but here does anybody anybody guess who this is
Let me see if anyone knows who it is
I
Thought the one about the Bible study that one made me laugh to be honest
You see didn't you see don't recognize but you don't recognize them that from the AI picture though
It may make sure you look too pretty. I was wondering if it was somebody else
I think she's pretty, but let me see, I guess I put her on my desk top, it's really hard
right now, I shouldn't have done the Danny stuff because it made me too sad, but yeah,
so yeah, this one right here.
Yeah, that one that's the one that made me open the maybe laugh I recognize. Well, it's like
That's kind of like her. It does a little bit. There's a little bit just like you obviously. It's obvious. Yeah, well
You know she is in well, yeah, because well, that's based on this clip
So I do have this short ready to go. So this was the short was posted nearby
Yeah, so what happened was I just like I was thinking about like
How it's like so crazy. It's almost like there must be like past life stuff and then like, you know, kind of like
Sub to you know, I am called a fake fake fake psychic or whatever like I guess, you know, she she's the
She knows, you know, who's bacon who's not even though she didn't she'd buy like 10, you know over 10 readings from me
But I'm sure you know she she knows but and she has the right to
To tell that right, but um, yeah, so I'm like community wall right here
This was a clip from the show. Do you remember this like this guy? God? He told me to have this guy in the show
His name is like he was like this clown. I forgot who this clown was called
The party clown. Oh, this guy's terrible. I mean, you can look at this, but here's a clip. This was great
But the clown is on the show and so you can't you can't see her in this clip, but you can hear her and
It's just kind of crazy
here. Just look through this one. Okay. So this is an interesting clip. Um, here. Yeah,
I don't know, but, um, yeah, you know, we have, but there are going to be like, I think
in the future, like some of these eunuch armies, like the army of Jezebel was a eunuch army,
right? And also, really? Yeah. I mean, Jezebel actually, she had eunuchs and that's actually
Jezebel at the end of her life like put all this makeup on to like it was like to go bite this prophet
I think his name was
Yeah, and then and then she got thrown out of her window by her eunuchs. I know that part. Yeah
It was interesting and also is like she was like trampled by horses eat my dog
And all that was left was just scrolling crossbones. That's like
The 3-2-2 thing, right? It's like, what do you think about all these? Like, there's a lot of
preachers who taught themselves as Christian preachers, but they're always saying that
Basically, if you're a woman who doesn't adhere to what their, you know, I guess, rules are,
you have a Jezebel spirit, I have been accused of having a Jezebel spirit.
I don't think I do.
If I do, well, it could happen.
Okay.
So that was Jezebel's spirit.
Correct.
Okay, so that explains it.
Yeah.
She's like, I don't think I do but if I do that could happen
I so because she's like going out for me today about Lilith like saying that now my cult is like, you know
sacrificing children because you know Lilith is like some child
Devouring demon or something like that and that and that like that basically
Which I never
Had an understanding of Lilith. I mean I did
Study Kabbalah and stuff, but I had more of an understanding of Lilith as this like figure of rebellion
You know the Adam she was like the first woman
I mean that God made next like equal to Adam
He made her out of like the desert sand or something and Adam out of it or the dust of the earth and then
Adam and her argued over who could be on top
And she wanted to be on top but Adam wanted to be on top and so she didn't want to be dominated by him
So she left the garden actually she didn't just like walk out of the garden. She said God's name. She said
like Yahweh Vahe or something like that and she flew up in the air and she like flew to the Red Sea and then
Some angels God sent some angels to go get her back and she was like hell no
I don't want to go back to him and so like these angels basically said okay. Well, she was like
basically all the
Babies that didn't make it like they were boarded or something like that like those were her children or things like that or like
Even further than that. Yes, but that was but that's also in this thing called the the book of Ben
Ben-sur-ah or something like that and which was the kind of a pseudographia like maybe the 15th century
It's a couple of cobblistic text. She was always kind of mentioned in the
Kabbalistic text there is a word the elite it means like screech owl in the button the Old Testament
There's that word one screech. I don't think it's the elite lily to but and then it's like Sumerians might have had a different
Thing like a way there were more wind spirits and things like that
But I've actually I actually always
I thought the character was very interesting, you know,
and that she was, you know, basically the first woman,
because in the Bible, it says,
God created them, man and woman.
And then later in the Bible, it says,
God created Eve out of the rib.
So it sounds like there was a woman created before Eve.
And so that's where the mid-Raj,
these rabbis, they would go through
and they found that word lalito
and they kind of like put together the story
of the first woman.
And then it turned into like Lilith Fair, it turned into like, you know, kind of like this symbol of empowerment of feminism and but also she had a relationship with gay guys too, because gay guys don't reproduce.
I kind of think, I kind of also look at her as like women that don't have children or that have like, you know, I don't know.
Interpretations, but she asked chat GPT about it. You know, she did a couple episodes of asking chat GPT and it's like basically like I'm
Need to be committed into it asylum. I'm just like I'm I'm I mean, it's just it was really bad
It's like there's just been such bad shit said
such hurtful shit, but it's like it's so
like
Feels like it was like every like thing that everything that they're on you
Yeah, everything is a villain, it's like I'm ugly because just to keep people away from me, I stink, I've covered in cat hair, I don't brush my teeth, even if she came and she took me to dinner and we had a good time and we had other places.
The whole reason, we were friends for months, months and months.
Like just like really close and I mean I mean she made an AI of me where I was like dirty on the couch with these
My cats are on top of me with these bags of money
And she like here's what psyche dreams about and stuff and I
Were friends at the time and I like I asked her about it. I just questioned her about it
like I returned against me and stuff and
She was like
She's like what like and then then she did turn against like that was it
I mean that was the reason because I asked her about it and then she said well
I'm talking to you again, and then I was like I was like what I was like
I'm sorry, and I was trying to apologize and I say that's pretty cold
Then it's like then turn into I'm a spiritual trafficker and then it's like
Then she doesn't call me like she calls everybody else. She hates him because she said it to a lot of people
But she calls out Joe. She calls everybody by their name usually the government name, but she just calls me fraudulent psychic
She says I'm like a stalker. She says she has all these women that they lined up
She said I'm gonna be basically beat up and or killed for for what I did and
Hold on
Well, I can read the definition of the Jezebel spirit real quick and how is my Civil War RP going?
It's feeling pretty good. I just play the Civil War RP in the
In the daytime sometimes like eight o'clock Eastern standard time
And yeah, just do that also been talking about geopolitical things too and like my things are mainly about military geopolitics and
Fishing and I got a kayak. I got a kayak. So I've been kayak fishing lately a mountain bike riding
That's what I do. I mountain bike at least six miles a day. It's pretty good
And it's not just flat. It's up and down here. So I'm going up and down six miles every single day
I've been doing that for about two weeks straight. I'm biking every day
exercising
doing my civil war role play and
I can read you guys definition of the Jezebel spirit
It is a concept of charismatic Christianity based on the biblical queen Jezebel representing a demonic force of manipulation, perversion and control is believed to threaten religious and political order by promoting immortality, aiming to dominate and destroy opposition is frequently used to vilify women in power.
Your mic is muted by the way.
There's also the the but the biblical story like if you know the biblical story of Ahab and Jezebel
That's an interesting story. I did not know that story. It plays Shilvery. Yeah, Shilvery too is a cool game
I bet Cycle liked Shilvery. It's a
It's sword fighting wink wink
And it's not that kind of sword. So I do
No, there's a story of Jezebel and Ahab and so she's this queen
And she, um, and Ahab was kind of like, Ahab is kind of like a simp, like he's kind of like, you know, dominated by her.
And like, so she tells him she's interested in this guy's property to go get this guy's property.
And the guy doesn't want to part with it.
I think it's like a vineyard.
And so he goes back to her.
And so she decides to like, basically set the sky up for a bunch of documents and shit and get the guy.
It's these I think stoned to death and so they claim the property and
Yeah, but she was fighting also with this prophet named Elijah. Elijah was the reincarnation of
Me see who came first. Yeah, so John was later the the reincarnation of Elijah like John is like John, you know, and then so
Elijah was constantly like fighting with her and so she had this eunuch army and
There's this time where she was like, you know, they're like trying to prove who's more powerful and so
She had all her unique army tried to like light just like this prey to get this like fire lit and stuff like that
and didn't like and
Then Elijah was able to light it or whatever. She always tried to kill this guy Elijah
He was kind of afraid of her and kind of hid from her too, but um
Eventually she did kind of meet the eye. She met a bad end and stuff like that
But, you know, Jezebel is like, Jeze means daughter, and then Belle is like, you know,
he means king, or ruler, or bell, or lord, you know, bell, ball.
It says that Unix, a Unix, were physically mutilated men serving as high-ranking officials.
They were attended to, managed to, comfort, and acted as her immediate assistants.
Yeah, and they ended up throwing her out the window at the end of it.
She, like, saw this other guy coming up to, like, arrest her or something like that.
And she, like, so she put on all this makeup.
And then they threw her out the window.
She was trampled by horses, eaten by dogs.
All that was left was a skull and crossbones.
That's the story in the Bible.
How do you know all this biblical, nah, you have a lot of biblical knowledge, how do you?
Yeah, I was like the closest to a Christian in my family that there was, you know, my
family's not very religious or interested in it very much at all, but I went to youth
groups and I actually, I loved the book of revelations when I was like young and I always
read the book of revelations and she's actually mentioned that book too, like Christ comes
back and he's like, you know.
I'm mad at you because you suffered, you suffered that woman Jezebel and you like, you know, put up, put up with her basically.
And so there's a lot of revelations about that, which is pretty interesting. I don't know.
I find it, the Bible, very interesting.
But I just think it's very, it's weird because she's calling me all these like false prophets or fraudulent psychic and the same thing.
And it's like
Can you see your dirt bike? Yeah, let's see the dirt bike. Let's do that. Oh, I have mountain bikes. I can show you my mountain bikes
So I don't have to get on my phone. Okay. Well, let's see right here right now
So do you see what's what are you doing with clumsy? You're dating him now?
That's I know I'm not dating close the clumsies always been like an acquaintance of mine because me and clumsy used to play
Call of Duty Modern Warfare 2 together and used to be on my panel time would do panels all the time
So I've known clumsy for like four years
Five years
Yeah, I remember you met him he was
He just always would tell prison stories and then debate people that would randomly join my call of duty channel and argue with each other
And then he became known as the broomstick guy because when he was in prison
Something about a broomstick in his ass
Yeah, it's so funny because it's like I never thought about like I was the other broom gang
I thought about room gang like I just like you know, I just think of like oh, that's it's interesting name for it
but then
When I you know, they did that ritual the other day with the spider when they flushed the spider down the toilet
They named it after me and stuff and they called it like the you know, be the and Christine and
And you have women doing rituals against you now. What is going on?
psych what is
and
Then yeah, and then they've been a whole trippy video where you know, they're all like dancing around fire and stuff
But um, yeah, I said that I said the stupid thing to Christine
Where I was like some of these like do you ever think that they're using you for ritual and I was like what as like I said
Oh, yeah, sure like you know
I just say I can see in my mind that they were all dancing or naked around the trees sacrificing babies and stuff
and then Kristie was there and so now she hates me again.
She actually was really mean to me
and this guy's Stephen King's chat today.
She came on, she was a mod too,
and she kept telling me,
fuck off, fuck off, you need to go to a mental institution.
Um, you know
Basically about to be arrested according to all of them. I basically there's always basically I've been stalking all these women apparently
Um, and I just won't leave them alone
Well, I mean, I really don't understand
I mean
The logic of it, but yeah, I guess I am I guess I am they're all saying it all the time, right? Um, so
How does one if you don't know these women in real life, how can they claim that it's just very far-fetched?
Okay, I go to their chats where I talk about them on the air and stuff so
But usually just they're talking about me for hours and hours. I mean they talk that
Spider rich really saw people for three hours in a row
They publicly live streamed themselves and then when somebody highlights what their live streaming or talks about it
Then that is stalking. No, just me. It's just me. Yeah, just just when I do
Yeah, so it seems like there's self victimization that they have going on
People can come to their own conclusion, but now they have like a you know, Christine has a new advocate
But it's really weird because you know, you think
That she would be against you know, you know, she's so you know, she's against witchcraft and stuff like you know
The other but she was saying oh, I love Christine and Christine's a witch and I'm a witch because I'm from this African tribe
Where we control the weather and stuff like that
but
control the weather. Yeah,
that's that's I guess that's
Native Americans to control
the weather with the rain.
There's an African tribe that
apparently that she's a part
of and she also said that good
times that I would use and we
should be thrown into an oven
and and she did the picture of
me like you know being burned
to death by be that in San
Manchu in a dumpster.
And it's or you can see it if you want. Oh, I mean, I showed it so many times, but I've noticed a lot of people have turned against the
Jewish people will lately because of the conflict with a Iran and all that
I don't know. I know it's like
Yeah, well, it went from like you couldn't like nobody really cared to now. It's like, yeah
Now they're putting psych into dumpster fire. Yeah, you can read what she said about it. That's that's supposed to be beat
You know beat in the sand man, I guess
Imagine claiming to be a powerful unknowledgeable practitioner, but failing to realize that your literal sacrifice to Jewish mysticism
rooted in ritual design to complete the process of manifesting what it lived with.
And Samuel, into this world, what the fuck is going on?
So that's like, oh yeah, well, if you see the one where I'm like, you know, hanging on a cross, there's one there's that one too, hold on.
Yeah, and uh...
Here I mean, I mean, it's like it's not it's not too insulting. It's you know, it's like what I think my abs look pretty good in it
But um, you know, it's just kind of like wondering
Why?
Well, this came but that's why I kind of like made the two you said you saw one you saw the two
I made and stuff. Yeah, but there she's made like she made two more than they was like the lila thing and about how like
you know
The first one made me laugh out loud and not going to lie, I was like, what the fuck is going on here?
I mean, everyone said it was funny. I mean, it's like, I guess it was funny, you know.
I mean, I think it would be if it was like, you know, me or me making something like that,
I probably would be in the institution by now, but you know, she said she said she's going to try to
have me 50-150 a few times, but I don't know, I don't think.
50-150, that's criminally insane. You're not criminally insane.
You don't go around robbing people and doing any of that slow. Oh
No, she said that I was approached by
They buy somebody with deep pockets apparently
to start
To start this cult or whatever to blackmail and
like spiritually traffic
Streamers and in the community for like their donators or something like that. And so that's what I'm up to
Okay, according to them and stuff
But uh, what do they know that you just decided to stream because people said you'd be a good streamer
Yeah, well you see but I mean remember I was friends with beauty at one point and stuff
Yeah, you had the tattoo you were friends with everybody
At the very beginning you were very very friendly with everyone and you liked at being everybody's friend and now it seems like
You've put up your spiritual guard around yourself like a
like like invisible walls
boundaries now before you
Well, I mean it's still like I still like I'm stupid enough to forgive like to like keep trying to like
apologize and like over and over and over and it's like
Getting to the point where it's like I'm done with that pretty much because it's gotten so far
But I don't know it's like it's just getting so like kind of mean mean
spirited I think like
It's kind of you ever thought about maybe like doing other types of stuff
Like are you gonna specifically stick to this type of panels or well, it's like not really like I can just like
Like what am I what would I do like I mean, it's like I mean, it's that's I don't know
I'd have to like get rid of my entire audience and stuff
And it's like I know I think maybe if you were to do like I remember the stream three would go walk around
We're pretty interesting
Yeah, I kind of do that a little bit like I walk around a little bit now it was still but
Maybe you like a mini Manson type of stream where you just start singing and put up a bunch of Christmas lights everywhere and
You start doing karaoke or something
Nobody likes anything I do. They just want to see it people. They just want to see people fight and
That stuff, you know
I do a lot of people are
I mean, I don't think that the people specifically. I mean, there are certain few who come here for that and
You know, I think this a lot of people are here for your personality mainly instead of
Other things a few people. Yeah
But you know, it's not going very well. It's just not going remember. I was like that used to go used to like, you know
You pretty like, you know, I would get you know a few donations here and there like people with you know
But yeah, I see what you're saying I
Know but it's like, you know, I know I still like I still can get pretty big crowds and stuff
I don't know. I guess all the pictures are gone. I get I still yeah, I still get pretty
Good-sized room sometimes, but it's like, you know, I remember when I say I used to start like disappearing like on the on the
Panels and stuff because it's like they're just like you like to yeah be toxic and you would just go behind stage and be like my
Yeah
Because like I'm really sent. I am really sensitive like
surprising like so like I don't know like I try to like
That's hard to say cold leader. Yeah, that's cool
Yeah, well, it's like, you know, the cult was always it was like not I just it was always like, you know
Just kind of like tongue-in-cheek and it was like I was always the only member of it
But um, you know, or I sometimes I call it cult of two because I ended up I did end up
You know having a digital daughter at one point or maybe it's still she's still around
but um, you know
She's still around somewhere behind this thing, but it's like, you know people said that was so weird, so
Kind of like, I don't really talk about her much anymore, but yeah, I don't know, and I have tons of content and stuff I've done, you know, I make a lot of stuff, but, you know, it just gets discouraged a little bit sometimes.
I can't find anything right now.
But I don't know. It's gotten so crazy. It's gotten so crazy, but I miss you though. I miss you though
I remember I want to go to tiktok because of tiktok. I can get like
20,000 likes, you know, even though you can be like what people like multiple times like one person can like just tap the screen but
The engagement is a lot better. Oh, yeah, there's no way there's like nobody likes
Like more people are just like in the now they made like them and stuff
Yeah, more people are just more present instead of like I notice on here like
You say something on YouTube and everybody is like trying to hold it against you
And then like you go on like take talk and like peep the audience is completely different the engagement is completely different
You can just talk and have good conversations on tick-tock. Whereas when you're on YouTube it is
definitely more
geared toward drama and
gossip
Well, yeah tiktok is like very like
Just random like people coming in like most people just come in for like a few like a few seconds and stuff in
Uh on tiktok, but and you know just it was going through but then I'll do people that will but be like really like
You know like you and stuff and that's pretty cool. I might see what's been going wrong
I could I was looking for like a fucking video and there's a picture
Have you thought about this those like so like you can do like so you know how people have like the mobile view of like stream yard
And then maybe do like a mobile view stream yard that would help with your engagement because a lot of people are doing these
Vertical type of streams, but I mean the podcast doesn't look as good. So I mean is your show so but that could be it
Yeah, I don't know if I can do vertical. I guess if I turn my camera like this
I don't know I used to stream for my phone, right? Oh here you know tell me James
Okay, I found the pictures finally like here's one of them. There you go. You can see that one
Imagine how bad this situation is about to get me. What are they are they trying to be me or dude?
They're trying to be me dude. That's not that's not that means you did say like last night that I would be
hurt very badly
Or something why did they use the word imagine so much?
That's her thing. I don't know who this Pierre Mellon is, but you're not cammed up
And I don't know who you are so you will not become on the show unless you do cam up or tell me who you are
Oh, then there's the one like I guess like, you know, she was dating Tommy James for a little bit, you know
But I guess like, you know, that didn't quite work out
But the good news for that is, you know, even though I'm not really into like, you know, ginger guys or whatever
But the good news is
apparently
Maybe they're friends of John Lennon, yeah, imagine they all end up with MC look
That Tommy James
Tommy James talks like this
Oh, hey, keep high, and I'm not talking about the cat lol. Oh, that's you
Hello
We said
Hello good
I'm London
We said
Where are you?
London good from London. Yeah, proper. How'd you find the show? We're what are you up to?
You're not good
Hello, so that again
You're doing good. Okay. I can't really understand you that well like you look you're you're like good
You're not you're not bad looking you. Oh my god. Oh my god. So you're a butthole
You're kidding me Jonathan. Yeah, I noticed that she was mad at me last night
I'm an old man. Yeah, you're an old man. Yeah proper, right? Yeah
Popeye
So, yes, like I would just come by to say what's up man, and I guess to see you. Thank you for coming
Or just saying what's up?
I'll see you. I'll see you again. I might join back if things get crazy. I'll stick around though. Yeah
See you
What do you say?
Well, that doing a shag?
You see, I'll put the London of this door in the night,
and you'd best make your snifter.
What's that all about?
Does anybody speak Japanese?
I'm not sure what language they're speaking.
Well, you fucking...
You do understand me.
I can understand you.
You do not understand me.
Let me turn on my microphone.
I choose to understand you. Okay. Okay. What do you want to say? What's what's your point?
What's up?
Hello
Hi, hi, hi, what why are you here? Like what's up?
I
A little bit difficult of a guess. I don't know. It can even help me out. I don't know.